We've got a third party...
Wearing sunglasses,
just out the window.
You're not
gonna kill me.
Good-bye, crow.
[ john ]
uh-uh, no.
You're not gonna kill me.
Good-bye, crow.
Wait!
[ glass shattering ]
Wait. Wait.
You say something,
chief?
No.
I'll get this one.
We got time
on this one, jad.
You mind going down
and getting me a piece
of cake they're eating?
I'm starving.
Sure, chief.
I think I'll get one
for myself
while I'm at it.
Take your time.
[ gunshot ]
[ dr. James ]
chief anderton,
what is this that I'm seeing?
I'm confused about--
[ gunshot ]
[ laughing ]
- Anderton, wait! Wait!
- Good-bye, crow.
- Anderton, wait!
- [ multiple gunshots ]
Anderton, wait!
I like you, chief.
You've always
been nice to me.